

Contact

Phone +90 507 871 3998

Email yavuzselimokur@gmail.com

Address Uskudar, Istanbul

Expertise

Game Design & Development

Project Management

Leadership

Narrative Design & Storytelling

Creative Direction & Worldbuilding

Language

English

Interests

Theatre

Basketball

YAVUZ SELIM OKUR

GAME DESIGNER & GAME DEVELOPER

I am Yavuz Selim. I've been trying to improve myself in game design and game development since 2016. I have made a variety of games on Unity Engine and Unreal Engine. I hope to be a person that shape the game industry in the future.

Experience

2023 – Present Spectrum Games

Game Designer & Game Developer

Designing and developing narrative and mechanics-driven games in a small, collaborative studio. Prototyping and implementing core gameplay systems to enhance player interaction and experience.

Aug 2019 - Nov 2019 Hi Games

Junior Game Developer

Developing hyper-casual and casual game mechanics.

2017- 2018 Istanbul Karsıyaka Basketball Club

Assistant Basketball Coach

Coaching for the children between 8 - 16

Education

2016 - 2022 Istanbul Bilgi University

Digital Game Design Bachelor

2017

Istanbul Bilgi University Digital Game Design Department is the first four-year BA degree programs in the field of digital gaming in Turkey. Focusing on digital games as expressive media, the program aims to educate game designers who are capable of blending creative thinking with technical and organizational skills.

Projects

Unity Projects

 World 23 (PC & Console) 	In Development
 Makrantia (PC & Console) 	2021
 Memoo (PC & Console) 	2020
 Picker3D - Clone (Mobile) 	2022
 <u>Uç ve Çarp (Mobile)</u> 	2020
 Run Cheff (Mobile) 	2020
 Assinment Yelleri (Browser) 	2020
 Meet In Dream(PC & Console) 	. 2019
 HyperBall (PC & Console) 	2017

Unreal Engine Projects

•	Need More Speed (PC & Console)	2019
•	<u>GiantDungeon (PC & Console)</u>	2018

Twine Project

The Good Saw (Browser)